<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250306052503 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/404197/20250306.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=404197&amp;date=20250306&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="404197">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR MOVIES HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250306013900 +0800" stop="20250306033000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Annabelle: Creation</title>
    <desc>A nun and her six orphans take shelter in the home of a dollmaker who lost his child 12 years ago. One day, one of the children discovers a sinister presence in the house.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250306033000 +0800" stop="20250306051500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Samson</title>
    <desc>Samson, a Hebrew with extraordinary strength, must use his God-given gift to rally his people to freedom from the evil Philistines.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250306051500 +0800" stop="20250306071500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mutant Python</title>
    <desc>In a secluded mountain village, a bride and groom celebrate their wedding. However, a monstrous python turns their dream day into a nightmare before terrorising the rest of the community.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250306071500 +0800" stop="20250306091500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Monster Hunt</title>
    <desc>In a world where humans and monsters are at odds with each other, a baby has the potential to bring the two factions together. However, its parents are forced to protect it from dangerous threats.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250306091500 +0800" stop="20250306104500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Frozen</title>
    <desc>Anna, the princess of the kingdom of Arendelle, sets out to find her estranged sister Elsa after she accidentally plunges their home into eternal winter with her power to create and control ice.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250306104500 +0800" stop="20250306123000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Night At The Museum</title>
    <desc>Larry, a night security guard at the Museum of Natural History, gets some help from the exhibits who come alive at night to foil a robbery attempt of a magic tablet and proves that he is not a loser.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250306123000 +0800" stop="20250307000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Tom and Jerry</title>
    <desc>Jerry, a mischievous mouse, takes refuge in a fancy hotel that is set to host a wedding. In order to get rid of him, one of the event planners hires Jerry's feline rival, Tom.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-06</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
