<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250207172610 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/404197/20250207.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=404197&amp;date=20250207&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="404197">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR MOVIES HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207005800 +0800" stop="20250207022100 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal Activity: The Ghost Dimension</title>
    <desc>When the Fleeges find some eerie old tapes and a camera in their new house, they realise that they have walked straight into a landmine of supernatural activities.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207022100 +0800" stop="20250207034600 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Guardians The Superheroes</title>
    <desc>During the Cold War, a scientist creates a team of superheroes in a secret science laboratory. When he turns villainous, the group unites to save the world from a disaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207034600 +0800" stop="20250207064500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Operation Red Sea</title>
    <desc>A Chinese special forces unit must rescue their fellow citizens in the country of Yewaire on the Arabian Peninsula amidst violent coup and threats from a terrorist group.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207064500 +0800" stop="20250207084500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Ride On</title>
    <desc>A washed-up stuntman and his horse get into a fight with debt collectors before escaping in grand fashion. As footage of the incident goes viral, the humiliated collectors seek revenge.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207084500 +0800" stop="20250207100000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic City</title>
    <desc>After the security of a top-secret laboratory is compromised, genetically modified dinosaurs get unleashed. Then, a black-ops unit is tasked with capturing the creatures before they cause more damage.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207100000 +0800" stop="20250207114500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Zathura: A Space Adventure</title>
    <desc>Two young brothers find themselves transported into the depths of space while playing a board game. They try their best to find their way back to Earth.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207114500 +0800" stop="20250207131500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Frozen II</title>
    <desc>Three years after her coronation when Elsa celebrates Autumn, she hears a mysterious voice. She follows that sound, along with Anna and their friends as they are forced to uncover the truth.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207131500 +0800" stop="20250207163000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Avatar: The Way Of Water</title>
    <desc>Jake Sully and his family lead blissful lives on Pandora. However, when a familiar enemy threatens their way of life, they must go to great lengths to keep each other safe.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207163000 +0800" stop="20250207180000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Home Alone 3</title>
    <desc>Eight-year-old Alex fends off thieves who are trying to acquire a top-secret computer chip that they have hidden in his toy car, with which they intend to help a terrorist group.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250207180000 +0800" stop="20250208000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Dinosaur</title>
    <desc>A rainstorm separates Arlo, a young Apatosaurus, from his family. While travelling through a harsh landscape, he befriends Spot, a feral child, who attempts to reunite Arlo with his family.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-07</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
