<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250307095703 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/404197/20250307.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=404197&amp;date=20250307&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="404197">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR MOVIES HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250307005300 +0800" stop="20250307030000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">World War Z</title>
    <desc>Gerry, a former United Nations employee, unexpectedly finds himself in a race against time as he investigates a threatening virus that turns humans into zombies.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250307030000 +0800" stop="20250307060000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Emergency Declaration</title>
    <desc>Aboard an international flight, when a terror attack threatens to transpire, havoc wreaks on the plane. The cabin crew must strive to save their passengers and themselves.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250307060000 +0800" stop="20250307080000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Operation Red Sea</title>
    <desc>A Chinese special forces unit must rescue their fellow citizens in the country of Yewaire on the Arabian Peninsula amidst violent coup and threats from a terrorist group.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250307080000 +0800" stop="20250307094500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Sword Master</title>
    <desc>A master swordsman is haunted by his greatest skill and simply wishes to live in peace. However, a rival who aims to take his place at all costs forces him to wield his weapon once again.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250307094500 +0800" stop="20250307114500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Beast</title>
    <desc>An enchantress, disguised as an old beggar, curses a selfish prince to live as a beast. To break her spell, he must learn to love and be loved before the last petal of the rose falls.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250307114500 +0800" stop="20250308000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Man of Steel</title>
    <desc>Clark learns about the source of his abilities and his real home when he enters a Kryptonian ship in the Artic. However, an old enemy follows him to Earth in search of a codex and brings destruction.</desc>
    <date>2025-03-07</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
