<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250215094954 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/404197/20250215.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=404197&amp;date=20250215&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="404197">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR MOVIES HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250215021500 +0800" stop="20250215034500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Into The Storm</title>
    <desc>Pete, a veteran storm chaser, travels to a town in hopes to film a series of developing storms. However, he learns that a tornado has shifted its course and is headed towards a high school.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250215034500 +0800" stop="20250215054500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Valerian and the City of a Thousand Planets</title>
    <desc>Valerian and Laureline, two special operatives for the space station of Alpha, have to protect the city from an evil force that threatens not only its existence, but the future of the universe.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250215054500 +0800" stop="20250215081500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">King of Serpent</title>
    <desc>On an expedition to learn about the species of an island full of snakes, a team encounters trouble in the form of evil hunters. They must strive to keep the isle safe.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250215081500 +0800" stop="20250215091500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Super Typhoon</title>
    <desc>A wrathful goddess unleashes a cataclysmic typhoon upon the world as punishment for humanity's transgressions. Panic ensues as people are forced to confront monstrous creatures amid the chaos.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250215091500 +0800" stop="20250215110000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Pokemon Detective Pikachu</title>
    <desc>Tim Goodman travels to Ryme City to settle the affairs of his late father. There, he meets an intelligent talking Pikachu and soon teams up with it to solve his father's last case.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250215110000 +0800" stop="20250215124500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Chronicles of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader</title>
    <desc>Siblings Edmund and Lucy return to the fantasy realm of Narnia with their cousin, Eustace. Soon, the trio embarks on a voyage across the seas with an old friend to rescue seven lords.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250215124500 +0800" stop="20250216000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic City</title>
    <desc>After the security of a top-secret laboratory is compromised, genetically modified dinosaurs get unleashed. Then, a black-ops unit is tasked with capturing the creatures before they cause more damage.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-15</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
