<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250224095619 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/404197/20250224.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=404197&amp;date=20250224&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="404197">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR MOVIES HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224010500 +0800" stop="20250224024900 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">XXX: Return Of Xander Cage</title>
    <desc>Xander Cage, a former xXx operative, is forced to return to active service to find and retrieve Pandora's Box, a satellite-controlling device, which gets stolen from the CIA's office in New York.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224024900 +0800" stop="20250224043800 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Monster Hunt</title>
    <desc>In a world where humans and monsters are at odds with each other, a baby has the potential to bring the two factions together. However, its parents are forced to protect it from dangerous threats.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224043800 +0800" stop="20250224044100 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Movie In Focus</title>
    <desc>A compilation of snippets of movies and behind-the-scene moments of films where the cast and crew share their on-set experiences.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224044100 +0800" stop="20250224070000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">She Wang</title>
    <desc>When a deadly serpent attacks several villagers, a group of hunters must find a solution to save the lives of people from the dangerous venom bites.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224070000 +0800" stop="20250224083000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Mermaid</title>
    <desc>Shan, a beautiful mermaid, attempts to kill Xuan, a businessman, by seducing him first but ends up falling in love with him.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224083000 +0800" stop="20250224100000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic City</title>
    <desc>After the security of a top-secret laboratory is compromised, genetically modified dinosaurs get unleashed. Then, a black-ops unit is tasked with capturing the creatures before they cause more damage.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224100000 +0800" stop="20250224113000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Ratatouille</title>
    <desc>Remy, a rat, aspires to become a renowned French chef. However, he fails to realise that people despise rodents and will never enjoy a meal cooked by him.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250224113000 +0800" stop="20250225000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Wreck-It Ralph</title>
    <desc>Ralph is tired of playing the role of a bad guy and embarks on a journey to become a video game hero. But Ralph accidentally lets loose a deadly enemy that threatens the entire arcade.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-24</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
