<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250218052256 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/404197/20250218.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=404197&amp;date=20250218&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="404197">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR MOVIES HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250218011000 +0800" stop="20250218025800 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Fall</title>
    <desc>Two best friends Becky and Hunter decide to climb a 2000-foot-tall, abandoned tower. Soon, they find themselves stranded on it after the corroded ladder breaks.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250218025800 +0800" stop="20250218045000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Monkey King 2</title>
    <desc>The Monkey King decides to accompany Tang Sanzang, a monk who aims to retrieve sacred scriptures. On their way, they encounter an evil demon who seeks immortality at great cost to Sanzang.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250218045000 +0800" stop="20250218050900 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Movie In Focus</title>
    <desc>A compilation of snippets of movies and behind-the-scene moments of films where the cast and crew share their on-set experiences.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250218050900 +0800" stop="20250218074500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Operation Red Sea</title>
    <desc>A Chinese special forces unit must rescue their fellow citizens in the country of Yewaire on the Arabian Peninsula amidst violent coup and threats from a terrorist group.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250218074500 +0800" stop="20250218093000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Conan The Barbarian</title>
    <desc>Conan, a Cimmerian warrior, seeks revenge against a warlord who attacked his village and killed his father. However, he soon realises that his kingdom faces a far greater threat.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250218093000 +0800" stop="20250218110000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Big Hero 6</title>
    <desc>Hiro, a robotics prodigy, joins hands with Baymax, a robot, to avenge his brother's death. Later, Hiro's friends join him, forming a team of high-tech heroes to help him in his mission.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250218110000 +0800" stop="20250219000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Maze Runner: The Death Cure</title>
    <desc>Thomas and his friends attempt to break into The Last City, a stronghold controlled by the evil WCKD. Soon, they try to free a companion from being imprisoned while finding a cure for a rare disease.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-18</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
