<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250228032059 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/404197/20250228.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=404197&amp;date=20250228&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="404197">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR MOVIES HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250228011500 +0800" stop="20250228024500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Aliens vs. Predator: Requiem</title>
    <desc>A small town in Colorado becomes a battleground for two warring species of aliens. One of them is a hybrid called the Predalien while the other is a veteran Predator dispatched to stop it.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250228024500 +0800" stop="20250228044500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mojin: Dragon Labyrinth</title>
    <desc>When four adventurers go astray in Gulan County, they chase the truth behind the red spot curse and try to find a way to undo it.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250228044500 +0800" stop="20250228063000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Adventurers</title>
    <desc>After five years of imprisonment, a notorious thief teams up with his partner to conduct a heist in Europe. However, tension rises as a French detective starts pursuing them.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250228063000 +0800" stop="20250228083000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Valerian and the City of a Thousand Planets</title>
    <desc>Valerian and Laureline, two special operatives for the space station of Alpha, have to protect the city from an evil force that threatens not only its existence, but the future of the universe.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250228083000 +0800" stop="20250228101500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Monkey King 2</title>
    <desc>The Monkey King decides to accompany Tang Sanzang, a monk who aims to retrieve sacred scriptures. On their way, they encounter an evil demon who seeks immortality at great cost to Sanzang.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250228101500 +0800" stop="20250228121500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Maleficent: Mistress of Evil</title>
    <desc>Maleficent alienates herself from Aurora when she opposes her engagement with Prince Phillip. Unknown to them, an enemy lurks, waiting to capitalise on their discord and destroy all that they love.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="404197" start="20250228121500 +0800" stop="20250301000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Big Hero 6</title>
    <desc>Hiro, a robotics prodigy, joins hands with Baymax, a robot, to avenge his brother's death. Later, Hiro's friends join him, forming a team of high-tech heroes to help him in his mission.</desc>
    <date>2025-02-28</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
