<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20260405113513 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/3290/20260405.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=3290&amp;date=20260405&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="3290">
    <display-name lang="Malaysia">iQIYI HD</display-name>
    <icon src="https://epg.pw/media/images/epg/2024/06/09/20240609085652963165_85.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405001000 +0800" stop="20260405013000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mrs. Golden Snake</title>
    <desc>The Sword Sect faces Lady Golden Snake's revival after her seal breaks. Demon Qu Ling and disciple Bian Xiaoya unite to reclaim the sword and seal her.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405013000 +0800" stop="20260405025000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Peak Confrontation</title>
    <desc>Gangster Chu Tian Kuo involuntarily participates in a competition to win the golden mask. But during the struggle for the mask, he is framed &amp; subsequently rescued by the princess of a foreign tribe.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405025000 +0800" stop="20260405043000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Ghost Mantis 2 Mutation</title>
    <desc>Entomologist Su Hao is kidnapped &amp; forced to participate in splicing experiments. To halt the inhumane experiments, Su Hao fights in a life-and-death battle against the demonic leader.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405043000 +0800" stop="20260405060000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Extreme Speed Police-The War on Drugs</title>
    <desc>Based on a true drug case, this gripping tale follows anti-narcotics officers risking their lives in deadly missions, vowing to wipe out drugs and safeguard the peace of the people.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405060000 +0800" stop="20260405070000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Swimsuit Saga Ep31</title>
    <desc>A hilarious nude swim mishap unveils a rollercoaster tale of swimwear startups. A pact with a wealthy future father-in-law spawns a swimwear mogul.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405070000 +0800" stop="20260405080000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Swimsuit Saga Ep32</title>
    <desc>A hilarious nude swim mishap unveils a rollercoaster tale of swimwear startups. A pact with a wealthy future father-in-law spawns a swimwear mogul.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405080000 +0800" stop="20260405093000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Sword Sovereign: Heavenbreaker</title>
    <desc>Many years ago, Jian Nan Tian is kidnapped by Xue Yu Lou while protecting the Sword Sect. Many years later, Xue Yu Lou strikes again, attacking the Sword Sect to capture Nan Tian's son, Jian Wu Shuang.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405093000 +0800" stop="20260405110000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">New Dragon Gate Inn</title>
    <desc>Set in the Ming Dynasty, due to a mysterious imperial edict, the general of the East China Sea, Zhou Huai'an, is tasked to escort orphan Qu Ling to the capital &amp; to await the Ghost Festival.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405110000 +0800" stop="20260405122000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Shuigui Bride</title>
    <desc>On a stormy night, 8 people gather in a dilapidated temple to take shelter from the rain. They begin discussing the legend of the Water Ghost Bride, kick-starting a series of mysterious murders.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405122000 +0800" stop="20260405134000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Snake</title>
    <desc>Despite the stories of a snake woman who devours those who venture into the mountains, the owner of the snake factory ignores the warning, leading his team into forbidden grounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405134000 +0800" stop="20260405145000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Guardian Of Graveyard</title>
    <desc>Treasure hunters Xun Ye, Feng Yao, Cai Qing Yun, Wang Ya Zi &amp; others encounter various dangers as they seek treasure at Qinling Phoenix Mountain, even averting conspiracies &amp; diplomatic issues.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405145000 +0800" stop="20260405160000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Shell Girl</title>
    <desc>Upon waking up in a laboratory, a girl finds that she has gained superior fighting skills but lost her memory. Hunted by an unknown man, she has to save herself &amp; rediscover her identity.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405160000 +0800" stop="20260405170000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">A Forbidden Marriage Ep03</title>
    <desc>Demon Sect's saintess Wang Yue is reborn after a near-death experience, becoming a humble orphan while holding onto her unfinished wish—to be with the righteous elder Yang Qing.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405170000 +0800" stop="20260405180000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">A Forbidden Marriage Ep04</title>
    <desc>Demon Sect's saintess Wang Yue is reborn after a near-death experience, becoming a humble orphan while holding onto her unfinished wish—to be with the righteous elder Yang Qing.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405180000 +0800" stop="20260405193000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Bride And The Beast</title>
    <desc>Every year, a young girl must be sacrificed to the mountain god or a curse would befall their small village. Two young men must now rescue their beloved when she is chosen to be sacrifice.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405193000 +0800" stop="20260405210000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Deer Travel Notes</title>
    <desc>After losing its family to humans, a young deer joins a bear-led alliance seeking revenge. But a chance meeting with a kind human changes its heart, leading it to bridge both sides and bring peace.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405210000 +0800" stop="20260405230000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Second Life</title>
    <desc>Years ago, a little boy is born in prison and his mother was forced to give him up, losing all contact with him. When she is released, she tries her best to make amends to rebuild their relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260405230000 +0800" stop="20260406000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Huang Jin Gui Shi Lu Film Series</title>
    <desc>With the influential sects at the brink of war, County Chief Lu instructs Chief Detective Duan Guang Long &amp; siblings, Xue Xiao Feng &amp; Xue Xiao Hua, to conduct a secret investigation on the matter.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-05</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260406004000 +0800" stop="20260406022500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Monstert Of Er Long Lake</title>
    <desc>Yu Huan wants to marry his childhood sweetheart Xiao Yu but is stopped by a huge bride price. With three goofy friends, he tries to raise money but accidentally awakens a century-old lake monster.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260406022500 +0800" stop="20260406034000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Red Land</title>
    <desc>Humans battle underground mutants "Headhunters" and the "Cave Tribe," fighting to survive and reclaim their home on the dangerous, resource-scarce surface.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260406034000 +0800" stop="20260406045000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Horror Legend Of Miao Ling</title>
    <desc>After the deaths of several people, allegedly from the Gu curse, Lu Wen Liang &amp; Zhang Chi Yi venture into the secluded village in the mountains to uncover the truth.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-06</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260406045000 +0800" stop="20260407000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mi Wu Ci Sha</title>
    <desc>The daughter of a late great general embarks on a journey for revenge when she discovers that the mastermind to the murder of her biological father is her foster father, the Prime Minister.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-06</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
