<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20250803104124 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/3290/20250803.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=3290&amp;date=20250803&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="3290">
    <display-name lang="Malaysia">iQIYI HD</display-name>
    <icon src="https://epg.pw/media/images/epg/2024/06/09/20240609085652963165_85.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803012000 +0800" stop="20250803030000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Sniper</title>
    <desc>Two formerly trafficked children trains to become deadly snipers to destroy the most powerful criminal organization in SEA and kill the leader of the organisation responsible for abducting them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803030000 +0800" stop="20250803044000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Detective Dee And The Punished Swellhead</title>
    <desc>When a mysterious curse causes people to undergo physical changes or be devoured by demonic beings, detective Dee is tasked with finding out the truth &amp; to resolve the impossible curse.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803044000 +0800" stop="20250803060000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Special Police and Snake Revenge</title>
    <desc>Set during the Tang Dynasty, the magistrate of Huanghe County, Wang Xuan, must uncover a sinister plot to prevent a city-wide massacre and save the emperor of Chang'An.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803060000 +0800" stop="20250803070000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Love You Seven Times Ep16</title>
    <desc>A celestial being and a divine lord are bound by an ancient red thread of destiny. Through seven cycles of love and hate, they experience a journey of romantic encounters across several lifetimes.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803070000 +0800" stop="20250803080000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Love You Seven Times Ep17</title>
    <desc>A celestial being and a divine lord are bound by an ancient red thread of destiny. Through seven cycles of love and hate, they experience a journey of romantic encounters across several lifetimes.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803080000 +0800" stop="20250803092000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Chi Dragon Slash</title>
    <desc>At the end of the Tang Dynasty, Navy General Qian Liu set off to exterminate the river pirates, only to discover a mystical two-headed beast called the Chi dragon in a cave.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803092000 +0800" stop="20250803104000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Caller</title>
    <desc>Two women, stuck in similar situations with abusive husbands, connected through a call despite being separated by time. Their budding relationship takes a dark turn when one of their fates changes.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803104000 +0800" stop="20250803120000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Tiger King Returns</title>
    <desc>After a village, which worshipped the White Tiger as its mountain deity, unexpectedly fell victim to a massacre by said tiger, the residents sought the help of a legendary hunter to resolve the matter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803120000 +0800" stop="20250803143000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">HAHAHAHAHA S5 Ep03</title>
    <desc>Led by Deng Chao, Chen He, Fan Zhi Yi, and Wang Mian, the "Five Ha" team travels through Xinjiang, Hainan, and Sichuan, blending comedy with local culture to showcase China's diverse folk traditions.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803143000 +0800" stop="20250803160000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Bride And The Beast</title>
    <desc>Every year, a young girl must be sacrificed to the mountain god or a curse would befall their small village. Two young men must now rescue their beloved when she is chosen to be sacrifice.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803160000 +0800" stop="20250803170000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">War of Faith Ep37</title>
    <desc>Wang Yi Bo, Li Qin and Wang Yang star in this series, where Wei Ruo Lai navigates the banking world, confronting personal challenges, with a fresh take on spy drama, integrating finance uniquely.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803170000 +0800" stop="20250803180000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">War of Faith Ep38</title>
    <desc>Wang Yi Bo, Li Qin and Wang Yang star in this series, where Wei Ruo Lai navigates the banking world, confronting personal challenges, with a fresh take on spy drama, integrating finance uniquely.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803180000 +0800" stop="20250803193000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Snowstorm</title>
    <desc>After a horrendous shooting incident on the street, Captain Zhou Yu Tong and his apprentice Wang Feng launch an investigation to track down the professional killer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803193000 +0800" stop="20250803210000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Fortune Teller</title>
    <desc>Zhao Da Chun is a well-known local psychic who privately joined forces with his younger brother to help fortune tellers solve practical problems, leading to many amusing situations.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803210000 +0800" stop="20250803233000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The King of Stand-Up Comedy Ep18</title>
    <desc>Initiated by Stephen Chow, the show features Guo Qi Lin, Francis Ng, Xu Zheng &amp; Yang Tian Zhen as team leaders, introducing hidden comedy talents competing for the title of Stand-Up Comedian of the Year.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250803233000 +0800" stop="20250804000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Land Of Women</title>
    <desc>The nine-tailed fox king Hua Yuan was sealed during the war. A century later, a kind &amp; innocent girl is betrayed by her father &amp; abandoned by her lover, causing immense resentment that breaks the seal.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250804010000 +0800" stop="20250804020500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Invisible Alien</title>
    <desc>The interstellar exploration spacecraft "Deep Space" that mysteriously disappeared 150 years ago suddenly appeared in low Earth orbit, with only a single survivor left.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-04</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250804020500 +0800" stop="20250804032000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mutation On Mars</title>
    <desc>When a seed bank at the base on Mars is threatened by a meteor shower, a team of duty-bound Chinese astronauts is dispatched to rescue the specimens, only to find a giant fish looking over them...</desc>
    <date>2025-08-04</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250804032000 +0800" stop="20250804044000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Ghost Mantis 2 Mutation</title>
    <desc>Entomologist Su Hao is kidnapped &amp; forced to participate in splicing experiments. To halt the inhumane experiments, Su Hao fights in a life-and-death battle against the demonic leader.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-04</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20250804044000 +0800" stop="20250805000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Vengeance</title>
    <desc>Unfortunate bride Yuan Ru Yi lost her entire family to a massacre on her wedding night. A year later, she embarks on an investigation to exact revenge on the people responsible for their deaths.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-04</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
