<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20260315112907 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/3290/20260315.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=3290&amp;date=20260315&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="3290">
    <display-name lang="Malaysia">iQIYI HD</display-name>
    <icon src="https://epg.pw/media/images/epg/2024/06/09/20240609085652963165_85.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315000000 +0800" stop="20260315013500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Hero</title>
    <desc>Dong Lu is kicked out by his wife &amp; becomes a basement manager through the introduction of his ex-classmate. His interest is peaked when he learns that there is hidden treasure in the basement.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315013500 +0800" stop="20260315030000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Agent 2: Peach Assassination</title>
    <desc>To invade the global financial system, a criminal organization kidnaps AI expert Fang Li. His wife, Ya Mei, a retired former ATO agent, rejoins the organization to rescue her husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315030000 +0800" stop="20260315043000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Treasure Hunting Of The Dragon In Shanghai Beach</title>
    <desc>At end of the 19th century, patriot hero Liang Chao entrusted his closest friend Li Tian Feng with the secrets to a hidden treasure, urging Li to unearth the treasure for the sake of the nation.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315043000 +0800" stop="20260315060000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Lost Destiny</title>
    <desc>While journeying to take the imperial exam, scholar Pu Song Ling meets Su Xian, a nine-tailed fox spirit indebted to his kindness in their previous life.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315060000 +0800" stop="20260315070000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Detective Chinatown 2 Ep05</title>
    <desc>Produced by Chen Si Cheng, this suspenseful detective drama features Roy Chiu, Shang Yu Xian and others in four thrilling storylines exploring urban mysteries.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315070000 +0800" stop="20260315080000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Detective Chinatown 2 Ep06</title>
    <desc>Produced by Chen Si Cheng, this suspenseful detective drama features Roy Chiu, Shang Yu Xian and others in four thrilling storylines exploring urban mysteries.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315080000 +0800" stop="20260315093000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Legend Of Feng Lou: Divine Fox</title>
    <desc>The grandfather of a human girl is killed after offending a fox fairy in the mountains. Years later, the girl marries Feng Lou, the murderer who killed her grandfather, in an attempt to take revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315093000 +0800" stop="20260315110000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Cursed Village</title>
    <desc>On their wedding night, Liu Jin is killed and Shen Xiu Xiu assaulted. Soon, men in Fengming Village die mysteriously in bridal attire. Chu Qi &amp; Xu Yi Ming search for her sister and uncover the truth.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315110000 +0800" stop="20260315122000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mrs. Golden Snake</title>
    <desc>The Sword Sect faces Lady Golden Snake's revival after her seal breaks. Demon Qu Ling and disciple Bian Xiaoya unite to reclaim the sword and seal her.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315122000 +0800" stop="20260315134000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Red Land</title>
    <desc>Humans battle underground mutants "Headhunters" and the "Cave Tribe," fighting to survive and reclaim their home on the dangerous, resource-scarce surface.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315134000 +0800" stop="20260315145000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Shell Girl</title>
    <desc>Upon waking up in a laboratory, a girl finds that she has gained superior fighting skills but lost her memory. Hunted by an unknown man, she has to save herself &amp; rediscover her identity.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315145000 +0800" stop="20260315160000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Horror Legend Of Miao Ling</title>
    <desc>After the deaths of several people, allegedly from the Gu curse, Lu Wen Liang &amp; Zhang Chi Yi venture into the secluded village in the mountains to uncover the truth.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315160000 +0800" stop="20260315170000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">A Love Never Lost Ep37</title>
    <desc>Amid chaos, five souls unite in Japan—royalty, rebels, and warriors—witnessing the fall of empire and the birth of a new era. Destiny calls in a revolution that changes China forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315170000 +0800" stop="20260315180000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">A Love Never Lost Ep38</title>
    <desc>Amid chaos, five souls unite in Japan—royalty, rebels, and warriors—witnessing the fall of empire and the birth of a new era. Destiny calls in a revolution that changes China forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315180000 +0800" stop="20260315193000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Desert Lone Hero</title>
    <desc>The fight for a mystical treasure begins after the death of Shen Shijie, the world's richest businessman, who built an impenetrable vault to seal up his huge wealth.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315193000 +0800" stop="20260315212000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Drug Storm</title>
    <desc>Vice-captain Xiao Ruolan falls into a trap at the border. Her substitute joins the police to fight Chen Qiang. Real vs fake, bullets fly—who will survive and have the last laugh?</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315212000 +0800" stop="20260315230000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Legend Of Man And Loong</title>
    <desc>The Huan Long family has lived with &amp; fought alongside dragons since ancient times. However, after a betrayal, all the dragon kings were sealed into the Nine Dragon Wall.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260315230000 +0800" stop="20260316000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mistery Of Error</title>
    <desc>Under siege from the feudal lords, emperor Zhou Su Wen relies on a special technique to transform himself in order to survive. Living in the village, he learns the meaning of responsibility &amp; justice.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260316003000 +0800" stop="20260316013500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Strange Beast Of Silent Island</title>
    <desc>Married couple Ye Bo Ming and Yi Lin are engaged in aquaculture on a remote island. During her cousin's visit, a strange bloodthirsty beast trapped in a mine is accidentally released.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260316013500 +0800" stop="20260316030000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">New Dragon Gate Inn</title>
    <desc>Set in the Ming Dynasty, due to a mysterious imperial edict, the general of the East China Sea, Zhou Huai'an, is tasked to escort orphan Qu Ling to the capital &amp; to await the Ghost Festival.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260316030000 +0800" stop="20260316043000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Special Monster</title>
    <desc>Gao Cheng set sail in search of an ancient ship carrying countless treasures that mysteriously vanished, only to end up on a mysterious island inhabited by a primitive tribe &amp; alien creatures.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260316043000 +0800" stop="20260317000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Bride And The Beast</title>
    <desc>Every year, a young girl must be sacrificed to the mountain god or a curse would befall their small village. Two young men must now rescue their beloved when she is chosen to be sacrifice.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-16</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
