<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<tv date="20260308210941 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/3290/20260308.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=3290&amp;date=20260308&amp;timezone=QXNpYS9UYWlwZWk=">
  <channel id="3290">
    <display-name lang="Malaysia">iQIYI HD</display-name>
    <icon src="https://epg.pw/media/images/epg/2024/06/09/20240609085652963165_85.png" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308000000 +0800" stop="20260308013500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">All The Initial Of Full Moon Scimitar</title>
    <desc>When a young man is betrayed by his first love and pushed off a cliff by his rival, he is set on a journey to learn a hidden swordmaster's technique to avenge himself.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308013500 +0800" stop="20260308030000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The Legend Of Feng Lou: Divine Fox</title>
    <desc>The grandfather of a human girl is killed after offending a fox fairy in the mountains. Years later, the girl marries Feng Lou, the murderer who killed her grandfather, in an attempt to take revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308030000 +0800" stop="20260308043000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mistery Of Error</title>
    <desc>Under siege from the feudal lords, emperor Zhou Su Wen relies on a special technique to transform himself in order to survive. Living in the village, he learns the meaning of responsibility &amp; justice.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308043000 +0800" stop="20260308060000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">The King Rise Again</title>
    <desc>During the struggle for the dragon throne, the Empress reveals that the Emperor has a hidden son. She appoints Man Shu to find the one who would be the true heir to the throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308060000 +0800" stop="20260308070000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Burning Flames Ep31</title>
    <desc>Based on 'Wu Geng Ji' anime, starring Ren Jia Lun, Xing Fei, Zhu Xu Dan and Zhu Zheng Ting. Prince Wu Geng, enslaved after his kingdom's fall, seeks revenge, leading humans against divine oppression.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308070000 +0800" stop="20260308080000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Burning Flames Ep32</title>
    <desc>Based on 'Wu Geng Ji' anime, starring Ren Jia Lun, Xing Fei, Zhu Xu Dan and Zhu Zheng Ting. Prince Wu Geng, enslaved after his kingdom's fall, seeks revenge, leading humans against divine oppression.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308080000 +0800" stop="20260308093000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Blade Of Fury</title>
    <desc>Pei Xing is famous for being an 'unkillable' &amp; cold-blooded assassin. But after witnessing great injustice, his dormant chivalry gradually awakens and he decides to retaliate in kind.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308093000 +0800" stop="20260308110000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Agent 2: Peach Assassination</title>
    <desc>To invade the global financial system, a criminal organization kidnaps AI expert Fang Li. His wife, Ya Mei, a retired former ATO agent, rejoins the organization to rescue her husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308110000 +0800" stop="20260308122000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Peak Confrontation</title>
    <desc>Gangster Chu Tian Kuo involuntarily participates in a competition to win the golden mask. But during the struggle for the mask, he is framed &amp; subsequently rescued by the princess of a foreign tribe.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308122000 +0800" stop="20260308141000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">To The Rescue</title>
    <desc>Upon discovering his girlfriend's disappearance, virologist Zhang Xuan travels to a foreign country to find her &amp; becoming involved with bringing down conspirators plotting a global pandemic.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308141000 +0800" stop="20260308160000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Monstert Of Er Long Lake</title>
    <desc>Yu Huan wants to marry his childhood sweetheart Xiao Yu but is stopped by a huge bride price. With three goofy friends, he tries to raise money but accidentally awakens a century-old lake monster.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308160000 +0800" stop="20260308170000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">A Love Never Lost Ep23</title>
    <desc>Amid chaos, five souls unite in Japan—royalty, rebels, and warriors—witnessing the fall of empire and the birth of a new era. Destiny calls in a revolution that changes China forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308170000 +0800" stop="20260308180000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">A Love Never Lost Ep24</title>
    <desc>Amid chaos, five souls unite in Japan—royalty, rebels, and warriors—witnessing the fall of empire and the birth of a new era. Destiny calls in a revolution that changes China forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308180000 +0800" stop="20260308193000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Special Monster</title>
    <desc>Gao Cheng set sail in search of an ancient ship carrying countless treasures that mysteriously vanished, only to end up on a mysterious island inhabited by a primitive tribe &amp; alien creatures.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308193000 +0800" stop="20260308210000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Mrs. Golden Snake</title>
    <desc>The Sword Sect faces Lady Golden Snake's revival after her seal breaks. Demon Qu Ling and disciple Bian Xiaoya unite to reclaim the sword and seal her.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308210000 +0800" stop="20260308222000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Shuigui Bride</title>
    <desc>On a stormy night, 8 people gather in a dilapidated temple to take shelter from the rain. They begin discussing the legend of the Water Ghost Bride, kick-starting a series of mysterious murders.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260308222000 +0800" stop="20260309000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Blocking The Horse</title>
    <desc>Ten years later after the death of General Yang Ye, Yang Ba Jie &amp; Yang Jiu Mei are determined to regain their father's lost treasured blade &amp; restore the glory of the Great Song Empire.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260309000000 +0800" stop="20260309013500 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Treasure Hunting Of The Dragon In Shanghai Beach</title>
    <desc>At end of the 19th century, patriot hero Liang Chao entrusted his closest friend Li Tian Feng with the secrets to a hidden treasure, urging Li to unearth the treasure for the sake of the nation.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260309013500 +0800" stop="20260309030000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Brotherhood Of Blades: Kill Evil</title>
    <desc>After a member of the powerful eunuch party dies suddenly and mysteriously, Chu Mo of the Imperial Guards is appointed to investigate the case, which leads him to reveal a conspiracy.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260309030000 +0800" stop="20260309043000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Desert Lone Hero</title>
    <desc>The fight for a mystical treasure begins after the death of Shen Shijie, the world's richest businessman, who built an impenetrable vault to seal up his huge wealth.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-09</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="3290" start="20260309043000 +0800" stop="20260310000000 +0800">
    <title lang="zh">Extreme Speed Police-The War on Drugs</title>
    <desc>Based on a true drug case, this gripping tale follows anti-narcotics officers risking their lives in deadly missions, vowing to wipe out drugs and safeguard the peace of the people.</desc>
    <date>2026-03-09</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
